Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Creative Services, 1964-2007; (80 boxes)
  - Subseries 9.1: Subjects, 1964-2000s
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Askyonov-Fink, 1982-circa 2000s (Box 50)
      Askyonov, Vassily; Ackerman, Helen (V.P. for University Relations); Alaire, Karen; Aronson, Susan / Bafundo, Donna / Barry, Jim / Bateson Mary; Bausch, Richard; Black, Murray; Blackwell, Avrana; Brenniger, Betsy; Brodski; James Buchanan / Nobel ceremony, Sweden; Clapsaddle, Jerry; D'Andrea, Paul (Robinson Professor); Dennins, Peter / Domzal, Teresa; Deklyver; Deshmukh, Marion; Eastman, Mike / Fagenson, Ellen; Feeg, Ronnie / Ferguson, Steph (Center for Health Policy)/ Findlay, Julia (Director International Programs); Fink, Richard
      color slides, black and white photographs, contact sheet, negatives
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Fuller-Kash, 1978-circa 2000s (Box 51)
      Fuller, Steve; Fried, Barbara (President of GMU Development 1998-1999); Fuentes, Carlos; Fukuyama, Francis / Gill, Bob / Given, Barbara (GSE); Grady, Mark / Griffith, Lloyd (Dean of Science & Technology); Hale, Janet / Hailey, Marjory; Harper, Doreen; Harvey, Jim (SOM); Hawkes, Robert; Haynes, Kingsley; Hazel, Til; Heastie, Joe / Heerschap, Marcelle (Dean of Admissions) / Herrity, John; High, Jack / Hill, Christopher / Hughes, Joy; Isbister, Jenefir; Jenkins, John (Police Chief); Jobbitt, Judith / Johnson, Gary; Johnson, George; Johnson, Manuel / Kash, Don
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals King-Struppa, 1980-circa 2000s (Box 52)
      King, Art / Klimoski, Richard (SOM); LaPorte, Todd; Lipsett / Luey, Jim / Maddox Peggy (Center for Health Policy); Maiello, Anthony / Matthews, Frank; McDonald, Heather / McDermott, Michael J.; Mellanders, Gus; Mielczarek, Eugenie; Char Miller; Miller, Rich / Morse, Gordon / Morowitz, Harold / Obrien, Alison; O'Conner, John; Olds, James / Palmer, Jim / Pendray, Jack; Perry, Wayne; Purple, Bill; Ratchford, Tom / Richard-Shieve, Susan; Rook, Susan / Rosenblum, Karen / Rudowsky; Sanders; Schoene, Les; Shirk, Joseph / Smith, Glen; Smith, Vernon; Sockett, Hugh; Stavis, Paul (Director of Law and Psychiatry Center); Stegmarci, Gerald; Stough, Roger / Streett, Sarah / Struppa, Daniel
      color slides, negatives, contact sheets
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Sugrue-Zenelis; Science & Technology; Miscellaneous, 1978-circa 2000s (Box 53)
      Sugrue, Tim (Associate Dean SOM) / Anita Taylor; Tillman, Betty; Tolchin, Susan (The Institute of Public Policy (TIPP) portrait); Westhead, Paul / Wilkins; Williams, Walter E.; Wood, Joe / unidentified man / Zenelis, Jon (Library); Science & Technology portraits (3 pages); Miscellaneous portraits (15 pages), copy work
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Cassara-Cook, 1984-1998 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Cassara, Ernest; Cassell, Cyrus (English); Censer, Jack (History); Cheldelin, Sandra (ICAR); Chen, Holly Ho (Chemistry); Chen, Jim (Science & Technology); Cheuse, Alan (English); Chickering, Art; Cilinski, Father Bob; Clapsaddle, Jerry; Clark, Robert (Chair, Public Affairs); Chris-Clark, Talley; Clements, Kevin (ICAR); Coffinberger, Richard (Accounting and Business Legal Studies); Cohen, Bill; Cohen, Lloyd (Law School Professor); Coleman, Steve (Law); Conlan, Timothy (TIPP); Connelly, Catherine (Cass) (Academic Program Coordinator GMU at ARL); Cook, Lisa (Education Study Center); Cook, Gerald (Electrical Engineering),
      black and white photographs, contact sheets
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Cooke-Damlich, 1985-1999 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      Cooke, Benson Dr. (Counselor); Cordell, Victor (Business Administration); Costello, John (Law School); Cowan, Tyler; Cozad, Mathew (Honor Committee); Crafton, Steve (Law School); Craig, Darrele (EEOC); Crain, Mark (Center fo Public Choice); Crandall, Bennett; Crawford, Dr. Peggy (Finance); Crawford, Michael (University Police); Crepeau, Richard (TIPP); Crockett, John (Business Administration); Cruz, Dulce (English); Cyphers, Glen (Director Physical Plant); Czarda, Larry (Executive Officer); D'Andrea, Paul (Robinson Professor); Dahlin, Betsy (Development Office); Damlich, Edward (Law School)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Davies-Donaldson, 1986-1998 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Davies, Keith M. (Chemistry); Davis, David (TIPP); Dawisha, Adeed (Public Affairs); Dawson, Ellen (Nursing, Student Health Center); DeBoer, Lloyd (Emeritus); Dede, Christopher (GSE); de Kluyver, Cornelius (Business Administration); Demulder, Elizabeth (Researchffilate, Associate Professor, Psychology); Denham, Susanne (Psychology); Denning, Peter (Computer Science); Denys, Martin (Philosophy and Religious studies); Diechio, Rick (Geology); Dick, Stanley; Dietz, Thomas (Sociology Fellow Associate Advancement of Science); Dinan, Desmond (Institute Institute); Dimock, Tami (Writer, University Publications); Dobson, Clark (GSE); Domzel, Teresa J. (Associate Dean School of Management); Donaldson, Jacqueline
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals D'Onofrio-Dworzecka, 1985-1999 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      D'Onofrio, Christine (Women's Center); Donovan, Tom (Physical Plant); Doyle, Elly (Center for Transportation and Land Policy); Doyle, Warren (Hemlock Overlook); Drewett, Ellen (Human Resources); Druckman, Daniel (ICAR); Duck, Lloyd; Duryea, Michelle (ICAR); Dzama, Mary Ann (Education); Dworzecka, Marie (Physics and Astronomy)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Eagle-Ferri, 1964-1999 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      Eagle, Steven (Law School); Eastman, Michael; Edelman, Marian W.; Ehrlich, Robert; Eland, Ellen F.; Eldredge, Susann (Print Services); Ellig, Jerome (Economics); Ellis, Mick; Ellsworth, Robert; Elstun, Esther (Foreign Languages and Literature); Emsley, Michael (Biology); English, John (Management); Entrikin, Richard (Marketing); Engebretson, Stan (Music); Ernst, Carl (Biology); Erwin, Amy (PTAP); Evans, John C. (Physics); Even, Amanda (Law); Ewell, Mary; Fagenson, Ellen (Business Administration); Farrell, George (Child Development Center); Feeg, Ronnie (Associate Director IOD Professor, Nursing and Health Science); Feinstein, Hyman (Chemistry, ret.); Ferri, Michael (Business Administration)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Ffolliott-Franseschi, 1984-1998 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Ffolliott, Shelia (Art History); Finkelstein, James (TIPP); First, Douglas R. (Environmental Safety); Fish, Michael (Sponsored programs); Fisher, James B.; Fisher, Klaus; Fisher, Myra (Nursing); Fleishman, Edwin (Dis. Vis. Professor Psychology); Fletcher, James J. (Philosophy & Religion, Academic Affairs); Flinn, Jane (Psychology); Fonseca, Jim (PWI); Fontana, Lynn (IDO); Forham, Jamie (UCIS); Forman, Joel; Foster, Gregory; Foster, John (English); Francescato, Martha P. (Foreign Languages and Literature); Franseschi, Teri (English)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Friedlander-Gillespie, 1983-1999 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Friedlander, Melvin (Public and International Affairs); Friedley, Sheryl (Communication); Froman, Wayne; Fulbrook, Jim Major (R.O.T.C. Director); Fuller, Stephen (TIPP); Fulmer, William (Dean School of Business); Fukuyama, Francis (MAIT); Gabel, Michael (Mathmatics); Gable, Wayne (Center for Market Processes); Gabriel, Arnald (Performing Arts); Gaffney, Kathleen; Gallehr, Don (Northern Virginia Writing Project); Galluzzo, Gary (Graduate School of Education); Gangloff, George (Admissions); Gantz, Donald (Oper. Res.); Gardar, Norm(?); Gartner, Harold (Public Affairs); Geller, Harold; Gellhorn, Ernest (Law School); Gentemann, Karen (Institutional Assessment); Gessner, Ted (Psychology); Giacomini, John (Law); Gibson, Craig (Fenwick Library); Gifford, Jonathan (The Institute of Public Policy (TIPP)); Gilbert Lewis, Paula (Foreign Languages and Literature); Gill, Bob; Gillespie, Norman (Law School)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Given-Hammond, 1984-1999 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Gilstrap, Robert (GSE); Ginsberg, Douglas H. (Law); Giunta, JohnGiven, Dr. Barbara (Education Study Center); Golamb, Louis (Sociology, Anthropology); Goodwin, Stephen (English); Goor, Mark (Graduate School of Education); Gordon, Linda; Gore, Irene; Gorrell, Jeff (GSE Dean); Gozikowski, Altona (Provost); Grady, Mark (Dean of Law School); Graham, Flo; Gras, Vernon (English); Greenberg, Irwin (Operations Research); Grotophorst, Wally (Library); Guagnano, Greg; Guillory, John (CSI); Guinier, Loni; Gulledge, Thomas (TIPP); Gunn, Betsy; Gurfein, Dr. Joe (Science and Tech II); Haack, Barry (GESS); Hale, Janet (Nursing); Hale, Jerre (Computing Systems and Operations); Haley, Marjorie Hall (President's Office); Hall-Long, Bethany (Nursing); Hamilton, Gayle (TIPP); Hammond, Mary Sayer (Art)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Hanson-Heinriques, 1985-1999 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Hanson, Margaret (Sponsored Programs); Harper, Doreen (Nursing); Harr, David; Harris, Carl (Operations Research); Harrison, Stan; Hart, Jayne; Hart, Joseph (Locksmith); Hart-Nibbing, Nand (Public Affairs); Hasse, Len; Haynes, Kingsley (TIPP); Hazel, James; Hazel, John Til; Hazel, William; Hazen, Robert (Robinson Professor); Heastie, Joe; Hecht, Leo (Foreign Language); Heclo, Hugh (Robinson Professor); Heerschap, Marcelle (Dean of Admissions); Heller, Kenneth (Graduate Business Institute); Henderson, Carol (Human Resources); Henriques, Peter (History Professor)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Herlihy-Hutton, 1985-1998 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Herlihy, Reid (Physical Plant); High, Jack (Economics); Hill, Christopher (Vice Provost for Research); Hillary, Adrienne (Student Accounts); Hinckley, Steven (Law School); Hirst, Omar; Hodges, Devon (English); Hoffman, Karla; Holisky, Dee Anne (English Department); Holbert, Harris L.; Holman, Emmett (Philosophy and Religion); Holt, Mack; Hoose, Virginia (Graduate Business Institute); Horan, Tom (TIPP); Horton, Lois (Sociology); Hughes, Joy (VP Information Technology); Hughes-Reese, Martha (President of the Nursing Chapter of the Mason Alumni Association); Harrington, James (TIPP); Hursh, Joseph (History); Hurst, Robert (Environmental Safety); Hurt, Charlene (Library); Hutton, Margaret
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Ingram-Johnson, 1986-1999 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Ingram, Earl (Vice President EEO and AA); Irvine, Lorna (English); Isenberg, Joan (Education); Jackson, Richard (ISO); Jackson, Scott E. (Library); Jackson, William (Physical Plant); Jacob, Evelyn (Education); Jacobs, Mark (Sociology and Anthropology); Jajodia, Sushil (Information and Software Systems); Janoski, Julie (Technology Business Alliance); Jeng-Eng Lin (Science & Technology); Jenkins, Agnes Courtney (Nursing); Jenkins, Jerry (UCIS); Jenner, Marti (Nursing); Jensen, Ronald (History); Jobbitt, Judith; Johnsen, Bruce (Law School); Johnson, Gary (TIPP)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals George and Joanne Johnson, 1980s-1990s (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Johnson, George; Johnson, Joanne
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Johnson-Kelly, 1983-1998 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Johnson, Jim; Johnson, Mark; Johnson-Brown, Hazel (Nursing); Johnston, Robert D. (Business Administration and Finance); Jonas, Robert (Biology); Jones, R. Chistian; Jordan, Shannon (Philosophy); Minas, Kafatos (Physics); Kanyan, Joseph (Music); Kaplan, Deborah (English); Karlson, Bob (English); Kaseman, Diane (Nursing); Kash, Donald (TIPP); Kavina, Milhailina (Writer, University Publications); Kazin, Alfred; Keever, David (Communication); Kehoe, Mike (Enterprise Center); Kehoe, Susan (AV Multimedia Producer); Mike Kelly
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Kelly-Krauss, 1984-1999 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Kelly, Mike F. (Physical Plant); Kelso, Don (Biology); Kendall-Hull, Margarida (Associate Professor Art Studio); Kendrick, Pat (Women's Volleyball Coach); Kovach, Kenneth (Business SBA); Kerns, Ruth (Library); Kerschbern, Larry (Information Systems and Systems Engineer); Khatchi, Borna (Physical Plant); Kiley, Thomas (Math); King, David J. (VP Academic Affairs); King, Patricia (Center for Human Disabilities); Kirby, David; Kirkland, Connie (Victim/Witness Assistance); Klappert, Peter (English); Klimoski, Richard (Dean of Arts and Sciences); Knight, Barbara (Public Affairs); Kobayashi, Bruce (Law School); Koda, Paul (Library); Korbel, Donna (Assistant Academic Coordinator Athletics); Kovacic, William (Law School); Krasnow, Shelly; Krauss, Michael (Law School)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Kravitz-Lawless, 1984-1997 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      Kravitz, Walter (Art); Krug, Robert; Kuebrick, David (English); Kurtz, Howard; Kwangyoung, Yi (Nursing); Laird, Nancy (Nursing); Lathburg, Roger (English); Langley, Chris (Nursing); Lankford, William (Physics); Lash, William (Law School); Laskey, Kathryn (Science & Technology); Laurey, James (Biology); Lavine, Thelma (Robinson Professor, Philosophy); Lavoie, Donald (Program on Social and Organizational Learning); Lawless, Sara (IOA)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals League-Looney, 1984-1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      League, Pete (SBA); Lebaron, Michelle (ICAR); Lecos, Mary Anne; Leith, Wilkie (Writing Center); Lepard, David; Lepore, Jim (Dance); Letsou, Peter (Law School); Levine, James (Foreign Language and Literature); Levine, Lawrence (History); Levy, Jack (Education); Levy, Ronald (Mathmatical Science); Lewis, Jim (Women's Basketball Coach); Liftman, Alvin; Liggio, Leonard (Institute Humane Studies); Lightfoot, Bill (Physical Plant); Lindsay, Pat (Mail Services Science & Technology Manager); Lipset, Seymour (MAIT); Littlefield, Elizabeth; Liu, Yuen Cha (Nursing); Lohner, Rainald (CSI); Lont, Cynthia (Communication); Looney, Sara (Ombudsman)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Loran-Martin, circa 1985-1998 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Lubar, Barbara (Events Management); Ludwick, Ann (TIPP); Lund, Nelson (Law School); Lynch, Edwin; Lynch, Michael; Lyons, Maggie; Maggio, Mark (TIPP); Mahler, Julianne (Public Affairs); Maiello, Anthony (Music); Malloy, Catherine (Nursing); Manchester, Bruce (FPAC, Communication); Mandes, Evans (IOA); Manne, Henry (Law School); Mao, Agnes (Library Administration); Martin, William
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Marsh-McIntyre, 1985-1998 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Marsh, Jay; Marvel, Linda (Music); Mason, George; Mattusch, Carol (Art History); Tawil, Max; McCrohan, Kevin (Business School Marketing Department); McDermott, Michael (Assistant Vice Provost); McDonald, Heather (Theater); McDiarmid, Dorothy; McIntyre, Cynthia (Physics)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals McIntyre-Melosh, 1986-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      McIntyre, Dianne (Visiting Dance Instructor); McKlancie, Margaret (Nursing); McMenamin, Lester (B & G); Mellander, Gus (Dean GSE); Mellander, Nelly; Melmed, Arthur (TIPP); Melosh, Barbara (English)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Sally and Alan Merten, 1996, October 4, 1997-February 25, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      Merten, Alan; Merten, Sally - general and copies numbered 1052B053-1052B055
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Mertz-Morris, 1986-1998 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Mertz, Michael; Metcalf, Jim (Nursing); Michalski, Ryszard (Science & Technology); Mielczarek, Eugenie (Physics); Milam, John (OIPR); Miles, Richard (University Police); Miller, Helen Hill; Miller, Linda (Dance); Miller, Mike (Library); Miller, Richard (Nursing); Miller, William (English); Millspaugh, Peter (Accounting); Mitchell, Christopher (ICAR); Mitchell, Sandy (SBA); Mobley, Marilyn (English); Mohle, Pete; Molin, Eric (English); Monas-Hattal, B. (VIT Prog.); Montebello, Mary; Montecino, Virginia; Moore, Jeanne (Nursing); Moore, John H.; Moore, Winston (Law); Moretz, Walter (Psychology Professor); Morowitz, Harold (Robinson Professor); Morris, Gilbert
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Morris-Nash, circa 1985-1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      Morris, Walter (Mathematics); Morrison, John S. (Graduate Business Institute); Mose, Douglas (Geology); Moses, Britt; Moylan, Tom (Center for Study of the Americas); Mulherin, Girard (Student Services); Mulpuri, Rao (Science & Technology); Murphy, Claudia (Dance); Murphy, Richard (Law School); Mushrush, George (Chemistry); Nadeau, Robert (English); Nash, Stephen (Operation Research and Engineering)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Nesbitt-Parisi, circa 1984-1999 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      Nesbitt, Archie (Physical Plant); Nguyen, Dr. Hung (Public and International Affairs); Normille, Lorette (Nursing); Norris, Eugene (Science & Technology); North, Dylan (?) C.; Oates, Karen (New Century College); O'Connor, John (English); O'Connor, Tom; Oerter, Robert; O'Hara, Erin (Law School); Orman, Evelyn; Owens, Coilin; Pacheco, Josephine (History); Paden, John (Robinson Professor, Public Affairs); Paelinck (TIPP); Palkovich, Ann (Sociology and Anthropology); Palmer, James (Information Technology); Pankey, Eric (English); Parisi, Francesco (Law School)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Parker-Raphael, circa 1985-1998 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Parker, Jeffrey (Law School); Pascarell, Rose (Women's Center); Pasnak, Robert (Psychology); Patrick, Sondra (Provost's Office); Pearce, Jack (Management); Pendray, Jack (Executive in Residence); Perry, Duke; Perry, Wayne (TIPP); Pfiffner, James (TIPP); Phillips, Samuel (Economics); Pocquette, Lynn; Posner, Marjorie; Potter, David; Price, Buffy (Dance); Pritchard, Edgar; Purple, Bill; Quinn, Camerine (Law School); Radar, Vicki (Sociology); Radner, John (English); Raphael, Coleman (Emeritus)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Raskin-Rockwood, circa 1985-1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      Raskin, Miriam S. (Social Work); Recycle for Life Workers; Redmond, Georgine (Nursing); Reeder, Bill; Regan, Priscilla (Public and International Affairs Professor); Rein, Laura (Library); Ribstein, Larry (Law School); Richards, Lilla (BOV); Rifkin, William (PSOL); Rine, David (Computer Science); Riordan, Patricia (Admissions); Riskind, John (Psychology); Ro, Young-Chan (Philosophy and Religion); Roback, Jennifer (Economics); Robb, Charles (Public Policy Professor); Robbins, Keith D. (SBA); Roberts, Ralph (Counseling Center); Robinson, Victoria (Career Development Center); Rockwood, Larry (Biology)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Rosenblum-Samuels, circa 1984-1996 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Rosenblum, Karen (VP of University Life); Rosenzweig, Roy (History Professor); Rossell, Dave (Provost's Office); Rossini, Frederick (Provost); Rothbard, Daniel (Philosophy and Religion); Rowley, Charles (Economics); Ruberstein, Richard (ICAR Professor); Rudowski, Lorraine (Nursing); Ruhling, Robert (Health Sports and Leisure); Ruth, Stephen); Sage, Andrew (Dean of Science & Technology); Samuels, Linda (Accounts, BULE)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Sanders-Sevon, circa 1984-1999 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Sanders, Art (University Police); Sanders, Warren; Sandole, Dennis (ICAR Professor); Sanford, James (Psychology); Saperstone, Stephen (Mathematics); Satija, Indu; Sauer, Tim (Mathematics); Schack, Fred (Physical Education); Schafer, David (Engineering); Schank, John (Computer Science); Scherrens, Maurice (Finance and Planning); Schmidt, Bill (Physical Plant); Schulte, Nancy (Student Services); Schultz, Martha (University Publications); Schum, David (Law School); Schopf, Paul (CSI); Schwartzstein, Linda (Law School); Scimecca, Joseph (Sociology); Seligman, Linda (Center for Study of the Americas); Seligman, Linda (Education); Setia, Sanjeer (Science & Technology); Sevon, Walt
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Shaffer-Smith, circa 1985-1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Shaffer, Jay (Biology); Shapiro, Jay (Mathematics); Shayka, Ron (Parking); Shields, Susan (Dance); Shirk, Joseph (Music Department); Shreve, Susan Richards (English); Sibley, Edgar (TIPP); Silva, Mary (Professor Nursing and Health Science); Sisodia, R. (Marketing); Skog, Judy (Biology); Slaght, Evelyn (Nursing); Slayden, Suzanne (Chemistry); Smith, Charles
      black and white photographs, contact sheets, negatives
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Smith-Spaldo, circa 1985-1996 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      Smith, Glenn; Smith, James G. (Music); Smith, Robert (Psychology); Sockett, Hugh (IET, Inc.); Soder, John (History); Sorrell, Jean (Associate Professor Nursing and Health Services); Soyfer, Valery; Spaldo, John (Director Student Unions)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Spikell-Sumser, circa 1986-1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Spikell, Mark A. (Graduate School of Education); Springford, Kate (Exchange); Spuhler, Raymond Hap (Athletics); Stadler, Walter (TIPP); Stampp, James (Budget); Stavis, Paul; Stearns, Maxwell (Law School); Stearns, Peter (Provost); Steen, Charles (Law School); Steenhuisen, Lauve (Philosophy and Religious Studies); Sterling, Donna; Stewart, Sheri; Story, Pat (PAGE); Stough, Roger; Struppa, Daniele (Dean of Arts and Sciences); Studd, Karen (Dance); Sudol, Carol (Student Health Center); Sugrue, Timothy (Associate Dean School of Management); Sumption, Eleanor; Sumser, Brian
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Swanson-Thompson, circa 1984-1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Swanson, David (Auxiliary Enterprises); Swope, Suzanne (Vice-Provost); Sypher, Eileen (English); Talley, Chris-Clark (Associate Director Alumni Affairs); Taub, Stephan (Biology Department); Tavani, N. J. (Sociology, Anthropology); Taylor, Anita (Communication); Thaiss, Christopher (English); Thomas, Charles (Education); Thomas, Mary; Thompson, Karen (Director of Development Krasnow Institute); Thompson, Lorin (President)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Timpf-Wade, 1986-1996 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      Timpf, Kimberly (Drug Education Center); Todd, Ellen (Art History); Tollison, Robert (Center for Public Choice); Tongren, Hale (Business Administration); Torzilli, Albert (Biology); Toups, John; Travis, Toni; Trefil, James (Physics); Trencher, Susan (Sociology and Anthropology); Trittipoe, Ben (Sports Information); Trump, Kathryn (Director of English Language Institute); Tso, Jim (BOV); Turner, Diane (Special Projects); Tuso, Hamdesa (ICAR); Twisdale (Law School); Van Buskirk, Ray (TIPP); Van Nispen, Frans (TIPP); Vandergriff, Morgan (Physical Plant); Vaughn, Karen (Economics); Vazquez, Diego (TIPP); Verheyen, Egon (Robinson Professor); Villella, Edward (Heritage Chair); Wade, Rex (History)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Wagner-Wiest, circa 1984-1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Wagner, Richard (Economics); Wahl, Otto; Wakef, Mary; Walker, Dr. Dorothy; Wallace, Susan (Director of Development Law School); Wallin, John (CSI); Wang, Pearl (Computer Science); Ward, Tom (Mail Room); Warfield, John (TIPP); Warfield, Wallace (ICAR); Warner, Keith (Foreign Language and Literature); Wegman, Ed; Wehrle, Walter (Philosophy and Religion); Weinberger, Steven; Weitzman, Lenore (Robinson Professor); Wechsler, Harry; Westhead, Paul (Men's Basketball); Westphal, Linda (Benefits Manager Human Services); White, Bernard (Science & Technology); White, Louise (TIPP); Whitney, Scott (School of Law); Wiest, Philip (Economics)
    - Admin/Faculty/Staff: Individuals Wiggins-Zoltek, circa 1984-1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Wiggins, David (Health Science); Wiggins, Brenda; Wilkins, Roger; Willett, James (Vice Provost); Williams, Anita; Williams, Carrington; Williams, Earle C. (President BDM International, Inc); Williams, Herma (GSE); Williams, Hope (Controller); Williams, Joyce (Nursing); Williams, Thomas (Sociology); Wilson, John (Biology); Wingblade, Ann; Witherspoon, John (Law School); Wong, David (Geography and Earth Systems); Wood, Jean (CAS); Wood, William (Alumni); Woods, Joe (Provost Academic Affairs); Wright, Brett (Nursing and Health Science); Wu, "Jenny" Chien-Yun (Professor Nursing and Health Sciences); Yance, Norman (Philosophy and Religious Studies); Yocum, Peggy (English); Zambrana, Ruth (Nursing); Zoltek, Stanley